foreign
[Music]
get out here you little pieces of [ __ ]
no we don't wanna let go damn it we're
going to be late come on [ __ ] bags
Sonic stop it stop it right now let go
now kids we had an agreement if you can
behave I just may let you stay late for
the office party
but Mama we don't want to go to your
office your work sucks more than Mandela
too at a strip club
I don't care I need to show you to my
new boss so he can see I'm a single
mother of three so he would take pity
and give me a raise
but last year you made us stand in the
hallway and you drove home without us
because you forgot we were there
what how come I don't remember such a
thing because you were drunk again
stupid mama
well whether you're happy with my
decision or not I'm most certainly not
going to allow you to stay home
this is an important day of the year to
prepare you for the grown-up world
and why doesn't Uncle Chuck take us to
his job instead
yeah Uncle Chuck always says he has the
best job in the world
can we mama I want to see what Uncle
Chuck does
Charles today is the day
today's the day you come clean and tell
the kids that you're a deadbeat and that
nobody likes you
foreign
if you think the kids will think lesser
of you because you don't have a job then
you're goddamn right
but you're making me look bad so get
your [ __ ] together and man up
Charles working at Target is like the
best job ever there's no way they'll
believe you
oh yes there we go ahead metallor
history
[Applause]
salutations father are you ready to
travel to Target for the annual take
your child to work day event
I don't want to can't I just play with
my chocks today
no father you promised you would take me
for the first time in our lives I've
dreamed of this day do not see
no I'd rather stay here and [ __ ] your
mom when she gets home from work
well you're not doing that
yeah how about to compromise if you can
behave and I don't got to spank you I'll
buy you that game company you've always
been asking about
um fine but only if we can get
McDonald's on the way back
well Uncle Chuck you work at Target why
didn't you ever tell us
don't you think
can we go inside
foreign
well I don't know how long you can keep
this up but I'll wish you luck
I'll be back at around three to pick you
guys up okay try not to get into any
trouble
problem
don't push your luck bro
thank you
don't drive away from me stop the car
not worry overall family
oh no I lost control of the car and
there's a kid in the road I can't stop
foreign
what the hell was that I don't know quit
sucking my balls so I can pull up my
pants and go check
hey you fat so what are you doing in the
electronics section
don't you dare ignore the regional
manager
it's cool my uncle owns the place
I've had enough of your lies dubby take
me to your parents so I can beat them up
yeah and I wanna suck your dad's balls
well Daddy I had fun with you today
as did I son
and as I promised I'll buy you one whole
video game company of your choosing
oh well how about that instead
it says it comes with multiple games in
one doesn't that sound fun we could take
turns playing it together
no I want Nintendo and Microsoft and
Sony
now dad don't get greedy I said we're
only buying you one today
but I want them
how about that one I hear their sexual
harassment in the workplace perhaps we
can get it on discount
no oh what's two is bad one was so much
better
enough of this if you are going to act
like a baby I'm going to treat you like
one no game companies for you today
for your punishment I am only buying you
10 video games at full price
God I hate this family I hate it why are
you doing this to me son
everywhere for your kids Uncle this man
is trying to steal your job can you tell
him to stop it
Quran dude you got anything to say I'm
all ass I mean I'm all ears
um
come on old man say it if you don't I
will
foreign
what are you doing here
you will compare your Visa foreign Delta
Uncle Chuck what the [ __ ] is he talking
about
you're not Sportacus he's Sportacus
foreign
let's hurry and check into our room I
don't want to be outside with these
creepy puppet looking people after
Nightfall oh they they're not so bad on
Earth taxi
Charles who thought you were a gay
prostitute
well yeah that sweet again
whatever I'll just take the bags up to
the room you go pickups in fast food I
would rather not use the hotel stove and
set off the fire alarm since you know
Mexicans tend to hide their drugs in
cheap hotels and [ __ ]
this place is
foreign
[Music]
wait that's sweet
your name is
oh
you're goddamn right I am [ __ ] boy now
help me out from under this car before
somebody sees me in this embarrassing
situation
you'll know what you don't think he's
old you as always
you're right you're right I am a failure
not a winner like George Washington
Elvis Presley or Michael Jackson
foreign
the number six
this number represents which sporticus
that I am
before me there were five others that
held the legendary name of Sportacus
over time each one would pass down the
torch to the next in line
after they completed their mission of
defending this town
they were all amazing especially number
five
when Sportacus 5 ran these streets
LazyTown went by the name of Awesome
Town
because it was just so [ __ ] awesome
to live here now it just sucks
to tell you the truth it may have been
my fault this town felt to ruin I
couldn't fill his shoes
yo
the citizens and the Sacred Apple Tree
of LazyTown they deny me
that's right that tree is where all
Sportacus get their power from
but don't get the wrong idea it ain't
free if you are not worthy of its power
the citizens of LazyTown will kill you
because you aren't fit as their hero
[Music]
wait distance
pretty much
Elvis
they don't wanna
please don't let me suffer such a fate
let me transfer my power into you and
then I'll be free of this curse meh
booty cold nevervees
I am dying and there isn't anyone else
around if you don't LazyTown is doomed
what muslimingo
for the powers of Sportacus to be
transferred over certain criterias must
be met
first of all the current Sportacus must
be anywhere between his early 20s and
late 30s
and the one receiving the blessing must
be a minor
from Minicraft
no like under 18. how old are you
17.
damn a little old for my preferences but
close enough
step two I must kiss you on your cheek
olvin that's all kind of guy
foreign whatever you want big boy
that's fine I would only want to do the
second option if you were 12.
the people of LazyTown are angry
we have to hurry up before they shoot us
with guns
[Music]
pictures
did it did it work tell me it worked
is
good and with this I die
my role is complete Charles promised me
promise me that you will save LazyTown
don't do what I did
no not Sportacus no more now I'm just
Brian Smith
[Music]
today
with your friends
well I was at first but my friend Robbie
has been acting very rotten lately
all he wants to do is make people smell
his ass he says it's the prank but I
don't know it just feels like bullying
to me so I try not to get in my alt
foreign
I wish he would stop acting so rotten
all the time we used to be such great
battles but I guess that's the thing of
the past
if you ask me you saw your literally
been stepping away
friends
hey you know what you're right I heard
he's gay a [ __ ] said it I'm gonna
start calling him Robbie Robinson as
homophobic slime that will teach him
that way he'll grow up to be an
alchemist of society and despise me
I'll work out and get muscles so I can
physically hurt him too
it's the code that's the same color as
[ __ ]
you don't deserve to be stored a kiss
you're too fat give it to me
foreign
no well it's still better looking than
yours because it looks a little bit less
like literal crap
that's root your mother was foreign
[Music]
who's
Market keyboard is overweight
poor old man
what are you talking about Uncle Chuck
you do have a job
no he doesn't
being the best uncle in the whole wide
world
no he's lying to make you feel better
and besides being a Sportacus for a few
hours is kind of like a job in itself
no it's not yeah I agree with Manic
shut up Sonia
[Music]
thank you
[ __ ] you
who are your kids
[Music]
I want a Whopper
spicy chicken fries
Burger King sucks
foreign
[Music]
that I need to spend my life here with
you
[Music]
foreign
I better with you
[Music]